Page	Line	Author	Date & Time	Comment	Reference Text
1	10	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/19/2023 13:25	PE-SA	"I've done a little bit of self-archiving and keeping track of like what the rules of the different journals that I've published in are so like tracking embargo periods, and knowing what versions I can post, where"
1	10	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/19/2023 13:28	KOP-SA	"keeping track of like what the rules of the different journals that I've published in are so like tracking embargo periods, and knowing what versions I can post, where"
1	10	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/19/2023 13:37	PW	I have some on a personal website. 
1	12	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/19/2023 13:41	LOA-IR	completely aware of what kind of institutional repository options are available to me
1	12	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/19/2023 13:56	R-UCSD	I have definitely used the CSDisseminate resources before
1	17	Austin Thompson	9/21/2023 15:38	U-OS	I don't know if this counts
1	18	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:25	PE-OA	"But if I have a a manuscript that was funded by NIH, and is now publicly available after the embargo period"
1	18	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:29	PE-NIH	"I have a a manuscript that was funded by NIH, and is now publicly available after the embargo period"
1	20	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:27	"PE-OA, PW"	"I've been putting links to it on my faculty web page, so that if somebody was to Google or look for my article and it was behind the paywall, the journal. They at least have a link then to it"
1	22	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:31	KOP-NIH	"They at least have a link then to it, for where where you have to deposit it for NIH, so they have the publicly available copy, not the pretty journal formatted copy."
1	22	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:10	U-OS	"So, I guess I don't know if that counts"
1	26	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:32	PE-OD	I have been involved in groups who have posted their data on OSF
1	28	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:37	U-OD	"I, personally, I’m just not sure like what I’m allowed to post, since, like I have a lot of recordings of children's voices and haven't specifically asked for permission to post their voice recordings online"
1	28	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:45	P-OD	haven't specifically asked for permission to post their voice recordings online
1	30	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:56	P-OD	"trying to figure out what I'm allowed to post and and share, and what I should keep private."
1	30	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:55	N-OD	"So, I I just feel a little bit nervous trying to figure out what I'm allowed to post and and share, and what I should keep private."
1	35	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:58	PE-OM	I have provided materials online that were used in my studies for researchers or clinicians who were interested in using them
1	35	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	6/28/2023 16:58	PE-OD	I've also submitted data to our RHD bank
1	37	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:13	SJ	"I've also submitted data to our RHD bank. So I've done through through them. I've I I know they're still. It's not a paywall, but at least there's, it's available to a lot of researchers there."
1	43	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 15:45	"PE-OM, PW"	I'd posted them on a lab website for other people who were interested in.
1	44	Danika Pfeiffer	8/8/2023 20:33	PE-SARP	"And I've also posted like after the fact, posters and links to like Powerpoint Presentation PDFs."
1	45	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 15:51	PW	After a talk I'll I'll try to post those on on my lab website as well.
2	3	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:10	U-OS	Do you include like open access journals in this?
2	4	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 16:04	PE-OA	"I have a article published in open access journal, which was is good. That's probably my most of my experience there"
2	13	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 16:11	A-CSD	I'm familiar with CSDisseminate.
2	14	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 16:13	Imp-OS	I know that open science is important
2	14	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 16:15	A-OS	I know that open science exists
2	15	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 16:17	LPE-OS	"I know that open science is important, and I know that open science exists. But I have not really taken the steps to do any of this myself."
2	20	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 16:31	PE-PR	I have just submitted my first pre-registration or report to OSF in the last year. This was my first time doing that. 
2	22	Austin Thompson	10/2/2023 15:30	"F-CS, F-PR"	"I'm working with a collaborator who is her job, she's like the Open Science librarian at the X, and so she's kind of walking me through all of it. "
2	28	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 17:01	KOP-PR	"we're really having to stick to what we said we were going to do in terms of the analyses that we set, you know we were like we are going to do these Bayesian tests, and only when we have enough power we'll be peek at the data, and it's been an interesting experience actually having to stick to those rules and and convincing everyone on the team that right, like there's a reason that we're doing that"
2	28	Austin Thompson	10/2/2023 15:31	"B-PR, B-CBI"	"it's been an interesting experience actually having to stick to those rules and and convincing everyone on the team that right, like there's a reason that we're doing that"
2	29	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 17:05	PE-PR	This is all very like new for me. 
2	30	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 17:08	E-OS	"But I was excited to do this because I feel like I'm just dipping my toe into this water, and kind of like experiencing it for the first time. "
2	36	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 17:30	PW	I have a website where I post all of my manuscripts.
2	37	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 17:30	PE-SA	"I do some self-archiving. I have a website where I post all of my manuscripts. I go to the CSDisseminate website to see, you know, like which journals let you post accepted copies and etc. "
2	37	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/5/2023 17:30	R-UCSD	"I go to the CSDisseminate website to see, you know, like which journals let you post accepted copies and etc. "
2	38	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:12	PE-SARP	"I post my, most of my presentation slides and posters on the same website,"
2	38	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:18	DUR	"I always offer to like, my data is available upon request,"
2	39	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:14	SJ	"I know that that's not as good as like sharing the data publicly,"
2	40	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:21	I-OD	"I know that that's not as good as like sharing the data publicly, and that's gonna be something I hope to do in the future."
2	40	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:22	DUR	But as for now it's just like upon request.
3	3	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:29	TE-PhD	"During my PhD, we had a weekly research meeting, and usually it was people sharing the research they were doing. But one year, one one week of the 5 years I was in my PhD someone presented on open science and recommended that we post our data onto OSF."
3	3	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:31	TE-OD	"But one year, one one week of the 5 years I was in my PhD someone presented on open science and recommended that we post our data onto OSF."
3	11	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:47	"R-UCSD, TE-W, TE-OS"	I went to one of those zoom CSDisseminate webinars that you had
3	15	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:50	"R-UCSD, TE-W, TE-OS"	I did the same
3	25	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:51	"TE-PhD, TE-OS"	"I think I have a similar experience to X, where we it was either like one class session or one colloquium meeting, and somebody presented on open science, and was like, hey, this is a good idea we should do more of this."
3	25	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 14:55	TE-NE	But it wasn't particularly extensive
3	32	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:08	"TE-PhD, TE-PR"	I recall that in our systematic review class we talked about sort of the registration of a systematic review protocol
3	33	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:08	U-OS	"I don't know if that would be considered open science, I think it would be"
3	34	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:10	TE-NE	"Originally I was going to say, I don't think I got any training in this. But as X and X who were talking, I recall that in our systematic review class we talked about sort of the registration of a systematic review protocol. And I don't know if that would be considered open science, I think it would be. And that's basically the extent to which it was ever discussed."
3	40	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:13	TE-NT	"I was gonna say I don't think I have ever attended a talk, or a webinar, or anything that was specifically about open science practices"
3	42	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:18	A-OD	"But it's just kind of maybe thrown in like if in a presentation, or you know a talk, someone will say, well, I use you know our RHD Bank, or whatever Aphasia Bank, so you should consider that as well."
3	43	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:19	TE-NT	I don't think I've ever had anything devoted to open science
3	43	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:19	TE-NE	Just kind of little bits and pieces along the way
4	5	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:20	WTL-OS	I would like to learn more about all of them
4	9	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:22	PE-OA	"The open open access paper that I published was because the Autism and Developmental Language Impairments Journal was like just getting started, and they sent out a like call for papers. That was like, if you submit within this window, we'll publish it for free, and then I missed the window. So, I had to send them the email. But that's really the only reason that it is published where it's published right now. "
4	9	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:24	F-OA	"That was like, if you submit within this window, we'll publish it for free, and then I missed the window. So, I had to send them the email. But that's really the only reason that it is published where it's published right now. "
4	10	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:26	WTL-OS	So really learning more about what is out there would be helpful.
4	18	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:10	WTL-OS	I echo that I'd like to learn more about all of these
4	19	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:10	WTL-OER	"and especially open educational resources, are something that I know very little about"
4	21	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:11	"WTL-OA, B-OA, B-M"	when it comes to gold open access I'd like to learn more about funding mechanisms because to publish gold open access is just so expensive and like what what's the best way to get that money?
4	25	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:12	WTL-OS	All of them.
4	27	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:13	WTL-OS	"Yeah, sorry, all of them. Yeah."
4	29	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:14	"N-OD, N-SA"	"I just am like nervous to venture too far into self-archiving and open data,"
4	30	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:15	"U-SA, U-OD"	because I'm just not sure what I'm legally allowed to do.
4	34	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:16	U-OER	I don't even know what open educational resources means.
4	34	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:16	WTL-OER	But I'm so interested by the name.
4	36	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:16	WTL-OS	I would I would agree with everybody who is saying all of them.
4	41	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:17	WTL-OER	"But I know that open educational resources is a really big push at my institution, because we are in sort of a lower SES area that people are really looking at the cost of attendance sort of beyond that, and trying to use as many open educational resources as possible. So I would say that that is definitely an area. If I had to pick one that would probably be the one that would be most relevant to my everyday life."
4	46	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:26	PE-OER	"We're, there's a really big push at my university now, where I'm I got on some task force too for open educational resources."
5	1	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:17	WTL-OER	"Yeah, same. We're, there's a really big push at my university now, where I'm I got on some task force too for open educational resources. But it would like to know more about our discipline specific and just not finding a lot out there"
5	2	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:18	WTL-OD	"and I guess, in terms of open data and how to work with your IRB on that specifically."
5	11	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:19	"WTL-OER, IOS-T"	"I've also been looking into open education resources. I teach phonetics, and I was like, oh, yeah, there's going to be tons of stuff out there, and the there is not as far...Yeah, right? So I guess I want to learn about finding resources and also about making resources. Like maybe about like networking with people and figuring out, wait like, how do we create that stuff so we can share? For our discipline. You know, for our classes."
5	15	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:19	WTL-OER	I'll go ahead and echo All of these calls for open educational resources
5	16	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:20	WTL-OA	and to a lesser extent like open access journals.
5	17	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:23	"WTL-PR, TE-PR, TE-NT"	But I would also like to single out pre-registration. I feel like I just missed that my doc program.
5	19	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:23	"U-PR, B-TE"	"And now that I've gone through and you know, graduated, I just. I don't know how to learn how to preregister things, and I feel like that's a a big gap in my personal knowledge."
5	24	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:24	"TE-NT, TE-PR"	"I don't think you missed it. I don't think it was there. I'm just gonna tell you like I don't think, yeah, I just don't think it was there."
5	25	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:25	"F-CS, F-PR, PE-PR"	"I yeah, I feel really lucky that I have this person. That's the only reason I'm doing it. And she's been like walking me through it. "
5	28	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:25	U-PR	"But I felt the same as you. I don't know that I would have done it on my own, because it felt like I was completely, well I was completely naive to what was supposed to go in there. And you know what are my goals from doing it?"
5	29	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:26	WTL-PR	"So yeah, I would like to learn more about it, too, so I can feel more confident about doing it myself."
5	34	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:27	"B-SD, B-PR, U-PR"	I feel like I don't know what to pre-register like I feel like my studies aren't big enough for important enough or using the right methods to preregister.
5	34	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:24	B-LOC	I feel like my studies aren't big enough for important enough or using the right methods to preregister.
5	40	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:28	"WTL-PR, WTL-OER"	I think that pre-registration and open educational resources would be the ones I'd be really most most interested in.
5	41	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:28	WTL-OS	But I think I agree also that they're all...I could probably use information about all of them.
5	42	Austin Thompson	7/26/2023 16:28	"WTL-PR, WTL-OER"	"But if I had to pick, you know, a couple of those would be the two I would pick."
5	44	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/13/2023 15:40	started coding first 3 responses for each question-whole group consensus	F
6	2	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:11	LP-S	The shorter the better
6	2	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:11	LP-H	Handouts
6	2	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:11	LP-V	a simple Youtube video
6	3	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:12	LP-S	To like keep it short and easy to fit into my life.
6	7	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:15	LP-A	Something that I can return to 
6	7	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:15	LP-S	"Something that I can return to also, like short"
6	7	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:15	LP-A	But also I can have access to it all the time
6	12	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:17	LP-H	I was thinking handouts 
6	12	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:20	LP-V	Youtube videos 
6	13	Austin Thompson	8/24/2023 16:34	LP-A	You know something I can do on my own time.
6	23	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:40	"LP-I, U-OS"	"Okay, I'm going to be Devil's advocate and say that I would like I would like something interactive, because sometimes I feel like...I don't know. I like when I look things up online, maybe my question is so so back, you know, like I'm, I'm. So I'm so novel. It's so new to me, or I'm such a you know I'm such a novice that, like I need to be able to ask questions to make sure I understand what we're talking about, and sometimes it's not. You know I'm basically I'm not gonna find the Youtube video that's gonna get me to the basic level that I need to be at. So I don't know."
6	25	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:41	"LP-I, LP-A"	"I also. I would like both. You know what I mean. I would like to attend something interactive where I can ask questions and then have things that I can return to later, you know, look-upable things are useful too."
6	29	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:42	LP-I	"Yeah, I I feel like that too. I need something interactive."
6	31	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:43	LP-HA	"Or I need like a working group where I'm accountable. Youtube is not gonna hold me accountable to like that open access, resource or something."
6	31	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:44	LP-I	So I do like something interactive.
6	33	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:45	LP-CP	I don't know if there was anything at ASHA. But if there was something that could be presented at conferences too.
6	44	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:46	"LP-I, LP-A"	"Yeah, I don't know. But something that I I think I do like the interactive more than if I If I feel like if I had it on Youtube like I would maybe try to fit it in, but it's always like I'll get to it versus like I have to be there at 7 o'clock."
7	2	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:47	LP-H	"I also agree that I think having the handouts, and everything is is great to have."
7	4	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:48	LP-CP	"But also, if there can be, you know, presentations at conferences. That's nice, because I've already carved out time to attend, and it would be a topic I would be interested in."
7	8	Austin Thompson	8/10/2023 14:01	"F-OS, F-CR"	"And even like a website. That would kind of be a resource for for a lot of these things. I don't know how possible that is, and who would fund it, etc., but something like that would be really good for you, because it could be constantly updated. It'd be one place to go to reach a lot of resources, you know."
7	8	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:48	LP-Web	"And even like a website. That would kind of be a resource for for a lot of these things. I don't know how possible that is, and who would fund it, etc., but something like that would be really good for you, because it could be constantly updated. It'd be one place to go to reach a lot of resources, you know. So, I think that those would all be great if they were if they were available."
7	13	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:50	"LP-I, LP-W"	But I was thinking sort of along the lines of we've talked about interactive workshops and in the interactive workshop I might think of questions. 
7	17	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:54	LP-PC	"But if a group like CSDisseminate, or something like that had like a contact person like. If there were a person that you could reach out to with a question. I have no idea about the feasibility of any of that,"
7	18	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:54	LP-W	"but that would be really cool to have a workshop,"
7	19	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:53	LP-I	"But what happens to me more often is I get really excited about something, and then I'll go back to do it and be like. Oh. I don't remember how to do this, and it's not very clear on the handout, so I have no idea if this is feasible. But if a group like CSDisseminate, or something like that had like a contact person like. If there were a person that you could reach out to with a question. I have no idea about the feasibility of any of that, but that would be really cool to have a workshop, and then have somebody that if something came up. You know who to ask and who to contact."
7	19	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 15:54	LP-PC	and then have somebody that if something came up. You know who to ask and who to contact.
7	30	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:45	B-W	Not knowing where to preregister 
7	31	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:46	B-CM	And concern that my methods and analysis plan will need to shift between preregistration and publication
7	31	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:40	B-PR	Not knowing where to preregister them is one. And concern that my methods and analysis plan will need to shift between preregistration and publication.
7	35	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:50	B-T	"For me it's time. I'm I have a pretty large teaching load, and it's for me sometimes it's like it's one more thing, and if I put something out there, someone I so right now I teach a 3-3 in the fall, because I just got tenured."
7	35	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:51	B-TL	"I'm I have a pretty large teaching load, and it's for me sometimes it's like it's one more thing, and if I put something out there, someone I so right now I teach a 3-3 in the fall, because I just got tenured. "
7	40	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:00	"B-T, B-R"	But it's the fact that I don't have as much time and resources
7	40	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:01	B-TL	being someone with a high teaching load at a very teaching focused university
7	41	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:02	B-T	So that's that's part of it is the the time factor
7	41	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 13:47	B-PR	"For me it's time. I'm I have a pretty large teaching load, and it's for me sometimes it's like it's one more thing, and if I put something out there, someone I so right now I teach a 3-3 in the fall, because I just got tenured. I will now teach a 4-4, and when I put something out there a a big lab could could do that. Would I what's gonna take me as somebody with a big teaching load with a 4-4 is gonna take me over a year. Somebody's got a lot of resources. It's gonna take them a couple of months, and for me sometimes it's just it's that was my idea, and not that I'm i'm scared of being beings scooped, or whatever. But it's the fact that I don't have as much time and resources, being someone with a high teaching load at a very teaching focused university. So that's that's part of it is the the time factor, and that that concern to be honest."
7	45	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:10	B-TL	"I also teach a 4-4, or I do teach a 4-4, "
8	2	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:09	B-T	"I also teach a 4-4, or I do teach a 4-4, and I feel like I have enough time. I have a really tough time carving out time for research as it is. So adding an additional step to the research processes like I said, it's going to make it less likely that things get done, and I'm having enough of a tough time getting things done, as it is. "
8	8	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:16	B-LOC	"I just<P>maybe I just have imposter syndrome or something, but I also don't feel very confident in develop...I obviously I have a PhD. Like, I know how to sort of develop research questions, hypotheses, methods, and an analysis plan. But I I again feel very anxious putting it out there for everybody else, especially like before I'm finished with it, because I feel like I might have missed something, or it just gives me a little bit of anxiety because I still don't feel super confident."
8	8	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:16	ANX-PR	"I again feel very anxious putting it out there for everybody else, especially like before I'm finished with it, because I feel like I might have missed something, or it just gives me a little bit of anxiety because I still don't feel super confident."
8	8	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:09	B-PR	"I also teach a 4-4, or I do teach a 4-4, and I feel like I have enough time. I have a really tough time carving out time for research as it is. So adding an additional step to the research processes like I said, it's going to make it less likely that things get done, and I'm having enough of a tough time getting things done, as it is. Also, sorry I didn't mean to cut somebody off. I just<P>maybe I just have imposter syndrome or something, but I also don't feel very confident in develop...I obviously I have a PhD. Like, I know how to sort of develop research questions, hypotheses, methods, and an analysis plan. But I I again feel very anxious putting it out there for everybody else, especially like before I'm finished with it, because I feel like I might have missed something, or it just gives me a little bit of anxiety because I still don't feel super confident."
8	18	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:10	B-CM	"My methods changed mid-dissertation. My analysis plan changed mid-dissertation. I know that's poor quality, because, you know, obviously I should have all of that outlined ahead of time, and I should be held accountable to following those, you know, procedures."
8	19	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 0:34	SJ	"But I just still feel like, hey, I'm a lousy researcher."
8	19	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:09	B-LOC	"My methods changed mid-dissertation. My analysis plan changed mid-dissertation. I know that's poor quality, because, you know, obviously I should have all of that outlined ahead of time, and I should be held accountable to following those, you know, procedures. But I just still feel like, hey, I'm a lousy researcher. My plan A probably isn't going to work out."
8	20	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:11	B-CM	My plan A probably isn't going to work out. You know. How do I shift away from something if it's preregistered and written in stone?
8	20	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:08	B-PR	"I defended my dissertation a year ago. For me research is still a learning process, and without being the most recent big research that I did. My methods changed mid-dissertation. My analysis plan changed mid-dissertation. I know that's poor quality, because, you know, obviously I should have all of that outlined ahead of time, and I should be held accountable to following those, you know, procedures. But I just still feel like, hey, I'm a lousy researcher. My plan A probably isn't going to work out. You know. How do I shift away from something if it's preregistered and written in stone?"
8	24	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:31	B-D	What everyone saying is making me realize that I think the biggest barriers is that we just aren't used to doing it. 
8	24	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:13	U-PR	What everyone saying is making me realize that I think the biggest barriers is that we just aren't used to doing it. We don't know what we're doing
8	25	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:18	TE-NT	"We don't know what we're doing, and we haven't been trained to do this this isn't how we've been taught to do research our entire, like"
8	28	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:34	B-D	"But you know this wasn't how we did research. What we did is, we would kind of come up with our analysis plans, you know, as we're going along."
8	31	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:19	B-TE	"this isn't how we've been taught to do research our entire, like. I think I'm kind of maybe on on the older end like I finished my, I started my PhD in 2006. I won't say when I finished it, but because it was a long time. But you know this wasn't how we did research. What we did is, we would kind of come up with our analysis plans, you know, as we're going along. And and you know which is yeah, maybe that's not what we're supposed to do, but that's kind of how I was trained to do it, you know, and it was like, oh, let's do a post. We even called a post hoc. It's like, oh, this correlation looks interesting. Let's see right?"
8	32	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:20	B-F	So there's something kind of scary about coming up with an analysis plan and sticking to it ahead of time. 
8	35	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:22	"PE-PR, B-CBI, B-CM"	"And like I said, I'm doing this for the first time right now. And it is it's interesting how I'm working with these two people, and I have one person who is not comfortable sticking to what we said we are going to do, and this is a very famous person in our field who is very well established."
8	36	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:31	B-TE	"But this is just like not what we've been, how we've been trained,"
8	37	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:31	SJ	"so it's not that we're bad researchers, or you know that are stuff is not important enough"
8	39	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:17	B-PR	"What everyone saying is making me realize that I think the biggest barriers is that we just aren't used to doing it. We don't know what we're doing, and we haven't been trained to do this this isn't how we've been taught to do research our entire, like. I think I'm kind of maybe on on the older end like I finished my, I started my PhD in 2006. I won't say when I finished it, but because it was a long time. But you know this wasn't how we did research. What we did is, we would kind of come up with our analysis plans, you know, as we're going along. And and you know which is yeah, maybe that's not what we're supposed to do, but that's kind of how I was trained to do it, you know, and it was like, oh, let's do a post. We even called a post hoc. It's like, oh, this correlation looks interesting. Let's see right? So there's something kind of scary about coming up with an analysis plan and sticking to it ahead of time. And like I said, I'm doing this for the first time right now. And it is it's interesting how I'm working with these two people, and I have one person who is not comfortable sticking to what we said we are going to do, and this is a very famous person in our field who is very well established. But this is just like not what we've been, how we've been trained, you guys, and so it's not that we're bad researchers, or you know that are stuff is not important enough. I was thinking about what you're talking about with time time, X, cause theoretically, this saves us time right, because, like you, you know, like you come up with what you're going to do, and you know."
8	39	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:33	IOS-ST	"I was thinking about what you're talking about with time time, X, cause theoretically, this saves us time right, because, like you, you know, like you come up with what you're going to do, and you know."
8	44	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:35	"B-PR, B-D"	"It's just this is so antithetical to how we've been doing research forever. I think that's what I feel like is the big barrier, you know."
9	9	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:18	"B-SA, B-KJP"	"5: I think the biggest one is just knowing like when it's allowed. If you know, if it's not really clear in the journal if that's okay, then that's the biggest barrier for me."
9	11	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:24	N-SA	I agree. I'm. I'm nervous about it. 
9	12	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:26	MUR	"So, for example, on Research Gate, I I will if someone messages me asking for a copy, I always send it to them, "
9	14	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:35	B-F	I don't know if journals are on Research Gate looking for academics to sue or whatever. But I don't want to find out. 
9	15	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:27	B-KJP	I don't make it publicly available just because I don't want. I don't know if journals are on Research Gate looking for academics to sue or whatever. But I don't want to find out. So that I think just the fact that each journal has very specific requirements makes me nervous.
9	15	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:27	N-SA	So that I think just the fact that each journal has very specific requirements makes me nervous. 
9	16	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:32	"PE-OA, KOP-NIH"	"So I think I'm comfortable sharing the the Pub Med, you know version, if that's available, for if it was an NIH funded study"
9	17	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:23	B-SA	"4: I agree. I'm. I'm nervous about it. So, for example, on Research Gate, I I will if someone messages me asking for a copy, I always send it to them, but I don't make it publicly available just because I don't want. I don't know if journals are on Research Gate looking for academics to sue or whatever. But I don't want to find out. So that I think just the fact that each journal has very specific requirements makes me nervous. So I think I'm comfortable sharing the the Pub Med, you know version, if that's available, for if it was an NIH funded study, but otherwise I I am a little...makes me nervous."
9	17	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:33	N-SA	I am a little...makes me nervous.
9	20	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:40	P-SA	"I do a lot of work as second author and third author, and that kind of thing. So I you know I need to get consent from the other authors"
9	20	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:43	U-SA	"I do a lot of work as second author and third author, and that kind of thing. So I you know I need to get consent from the other authors. At least I feel like. "
9	21	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:46	B-AM	But then often I'm depending on them to send me the accepted manuscript. And either they don't get around to it
9	22	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:49	B-CBI	"or don't feel like it, or they're not on board, so that's been a barrier that I've encountered."
9	22	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/17/2023 14:33	B-SA	"8: I do a lot of work as second author and third author, and that kind of thing. So I you know I need to get consent from the other authors. At least I feel like. But then often I'm depending on them to send me the accepted manuscript. And either they don't get around to it, or don't feel like it, or they're not on board, so that's been a barrier that I've encountered."
9	25	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:36	B-R	"We don't have a really robust lab website. I don't have a personal website,"
9	26	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:41	B-CX	so it just seems like there's multiple steps that even if I got something published which I don't have many publications.
9	27	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:42	B-T	"So that's part one is the issue that again, the time to have manuscripts that I can publish and self- archive."
9	29	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:43	B-CX	"But then the process of like creating the the website or the repository, or wherever it's going to be. It just seems like there's multiple steps,"
9	31	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:43	B-NE	"none of them are pressing, and I don't know about anybody else, but I really respond well to deadlines and pressure, and so this never has a deadline or pressure, so it's never at the top of my list."
9	31	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:35	B-SA	"We don't have a really robust lab website. I don't have a personal website, so it just seems like there's multiple steps that even if I got something published which I don't have many publications. So that's part one is the issue that again, the time to have manuscripts that I can publish and self- archive. But then the process of like creating the the website or the repository, or wherever it's going to be. It just seems like there's multiple steps, and none of them are pressing, and I don't know about anybody else, but I really respond well to deadlines and pressure, and so this never has a deadline or pressure, so it's never at the top of my list."
9	35	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:45	U-SA	I don't know what I'm allowed to do
9	37	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:46	B-KJP	"I don't know what I'm allowed to do, and I like...every journal has different rules, so it's not even like I can just say like, oh, I'm allowed to do X. Because ASHA has a different rule compared to you know, Clinical Linguistics and Phonetics, "
9	39	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:44	B-SA	"No, just I I don't know what I'm allowed to do, and I like...every journal has different rules, so it's not even like I can just say like, oh, I'm allowed to do X. Because ASHA has a different rule compared to you know, Clinical Linguistics and Phonetics, and I just. I just don't wanna get sued for sharing my own work that I that I worked on it's a little bit ridiculous that we're not allowed to share our own work."
9	39	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:48	B-F	I just don't wanna get sued for sharing my own work that I that I worked on it's a little bit ridiculous that we're not allowed to share our own work. 
9	46	Danika Pfeiffer	7/25/2023 20:49	"F-SA, F-CR"	"If there is just a one place, I could go and look up the journal, and it would just say what their policy was that would help"
10	9	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 0:31	"LP-H, F-CR"	"If there were a handout saying like, you know, I think I think someone just said this, but like the journal name, what I am allowed to do legally and just someone explain it to me, and just very easy to understand language that I can be sure I'm not breaking some copyright"
10	9	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:05	F-SA	" I mean the like. If there were a handout saying like, you know, I think I think someone just said this, but like the journal name, what I am allowed to do legally and just someone explain it to me, and just very easy to understand language that I can be sure I'm not breaking some copyright."
10	14	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 0:32	"F-SA, F-CR"	"It would be nice if journals made that information, like every journal has their policy on it, and you can find it."
10	14	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:11	B-CX	"But it's so many steps, and like clicking and digging through everything"
10	24	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:12	"B-PR, B-CM"	": Yeah I mean, it goes back to what someone is saying about like you're not sure what you're gonna do with the stats like. You might make some statistical decision, and it's not the right one. "
10	30	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:24	"F-PR, F-DC"	"And so like, even like I feel like if I already have my data, I feel much more confident about my stats plan. Then, like if I'm hoping to collect some amount of data. So like, really, where I am in the process, like if I pre-register something, hoping that I'll be able to get, you know, 120 kids, but I only get 60 like that. Like I'm not going to be able to do the same statistical analyses all the time, so like. I think it just depends on where I am in the process of data collection, and like preregistering before I even collect any data. I'm not sure I I want to maintain that that same approach after I get the data"
10	37	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:34	"U-PR, F-ACM"	"Something that would help facilitate for me is is what you're allowed to say in terms of exploratory or like, you know this is like, is it a flow...Can I put a flow chart like if I have this many kids? This is what I'll do. But if I have this many, you know what I mean, and and there are things you can do like you are allowed to say those things. Like this is what I would do in this event. "
10	39	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:39	F-TE	"what would facilitate it would be like training. I just need to learn what's allowed. I need to learn what you can say, "
10	39	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:40	TE-NE	I don't think many of us have had that training
10	39	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:30	F-PR	"Something that would help facilitate for me is is what you're allowed to say in terms of exploratory or like, you know this is like, is it a flow...Can I put a flow chart like if I have this many kids? This is what I'll do. But if I have this many, you know what I mean, and and there are things you can do like you are allowed to say those things. Like this is what I would do in this event. But if this doesn't happen, but I but if you haven't so again like what would facilitate it would be like training. I just need to learn what's allowed. I need to learn what you can say, you know, and I just again. I don't think many of us have had that training."
10	44	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:48	"B-PR, B-SD, U-PR"	"I do a lot of qualitative work, and, like your research questions can change once you have started analysis, so I feel like the rules become even less clear, and that makes it harder to preregister qualitative studies"
11	14	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:13	"F-PR, F-SD"	"Ok, I was just gonna say I think I often do is I keep doing studies that are quite different from ones I've done previously, which is, I suppose, good on some levels, but on an another, I think if I was doing a study that was very similar with similar methods. Similar population. You know, and I knew kind of I could kind of predict like, yes, I'll easily be able to get these participants, and so on. I think I'd be more likely if it was just really similar to something I'd done previously. I'd be more likely to be comfortable pre-registering something just kind of having walked through the analysis, having some knowledge of what you know that I've gotten through those barriers that would be concerning. And I I wonder if it's something I would be more likely to do in the future, just because, as I get more comfortable with, if I ever stop doing studies that are totally different, take more time than they should, because I insist on doing something else. I don't know."
11	22	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:50	"B-OA, B-M"	Money is really the only barrier. As far as I can tell.
11	27	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 15:55	"PE-NIH, B-WR, B-OA"	"My post doc advisor. She never wanted to pay open access fees because we always had to submit everything to to NIH eventually, anyway. So she thought like, why would we spend our money on this when eventually it will be public? So I mean, that was kind of like you're going to do it, anyway. So why are we going to pay $4,000 to do it now?"
11	33	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:18	U-OA	This is probably a really naive question. But what is the difference between what makes it gold open access as compared to other levels?
11	42	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:19	U-OA	Thanks. I knew the money was an issue. I just didn't know the difference. 
12	4	Brittany Ciullo	8/23/2023 14:04	"B-OA, B-M, B-R"	"I tried to write funds for open access, publishing into my startup, and I was denied so. But I guess that would be a barrier, but it would have helped. "
12	4	Brittany Ciullo	8/23/2023 14:08	"Note: this used to be B-OA, B-M, B-LIS. Removed B-LIS code and replaced with B-R."	"I tried to write funds for open access, publishing into my startup, and I was denied so. But I guess that would be a barrier, but it would have helped. "
12	12	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:23	F-M	"a couple of times where I'm faculty now and then where I did my postdoc. They, the libraries of those institutions, promoted a deal that they had with a specific publisher, where they were for a certain period of time gonna offer free open access. And I certainly took advantage of that. And specifically, you know, went and picked a journal that was within that publishing suite. So that was great because it was free."
12	14	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:21	"F-OA, PE-OA, F-IS"	"a couple of times where I'm faculty now and then where I did my postdoc. They, the libraries of those institutions, promoted a deal that they had with a specific publisher, where they were for a certain period of time gonna offer free open access. And I certainly took advantage of that. And specifically, you know, went and picked a journal that was within that publishing suite. So that was great because it was free. But it was that was offered through the institution, and I have no idea like what on the back end was happening, but the library promoted it, and both cases, and I took advantage of it."
12	18	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:30	B-M	Open access fees...The gold open access fees cost more than I'm allotted for research each year. 
12	19	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:29	B-NE	I work at a teaching school. Open access fees...The gold open access fees cost more than I'm allotted for research each year. I don't care that much about impact factors. I just want my words on paper. I don't need to submit to the top tier journals. 
12	21	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:29	B-OA	"I'll just throw this out there. I'm realistic about my lot in life. I work at a teaching school. Open access fees...The gold open access fees cost more than I'm allotted for research each year. I don't care that much about impact factors. I just want my words on paper. I don't need to submit to the top tier journals. I would be happy submitting to like the open access, CSD journal, if somebody would, you know, peer review and publish my work and share it with a, you know, students and faculty in our field across the country, and wherever."
12	30	Austin Thompson	7/31/2023 18:32	"F-OA, F-M, F-IS, PE-OA"	"I was just gonna say, my dean at my current institution did advertise that she was also willing in some cases to pay open access fees so to contact her if you had a journal where that would be appropriate, and she would consider it depending on I assuming impact factor, and so on. But that was something I I don't know if that's common, but I was surprised to hear it."
12	43	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:07	"B-OD, B-CR"	"I can just talk about one specific barrier that I've experienced, which is, I am my dissertation, study, or part of my dissertation study was a replication of somebody else's work with a slightly different population and slightly different methods. And so, when I wanted to share some of those methods, they were still under copyright from their from their published work, they they had given them to me so that I could use them. But I couldn't share them sort of openly and publicly. So that was a barrier that I've experienced."
12	46	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:09	"B-OD, B-IRB"	"My IRB is not willing to let me put anything online like I've I've asked their permission to put things on on like the childes database website, and they refuse."
13	6	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:17	PE-OD	"Somebody earlier mentioned participant consent. Which I think, as as I grow as a researcher and my awareness of open science practices, grows. I'm starting to build that into consent processes. "
13	8	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:12	B-OD	"Somebody earlier mentioned participant consent. Which I think, as as I grow as a researcher and my awareness of open science practices, grows. I'm starting to build that into consent processes. But you know, for studies that have already been done like you can't retroactively do it, so that I think just getting participant consent, and having the mechanisms in place to do it can be potentially a barrier"
13	8	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:17	P-OD	"But you know, for studies that have already been done like you can't retroactively do it, so that I think just getting participant consent, and having the mechanisms in place to do it can be potentially a barrier."
13	13	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 22:40	B-ID	"It would be that almost to the point where you could potentially figure out who they are, if you know where the study was conducted, and kind of some of the specifics of their disease"
13	14	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 22:39	"B-OD, N-OD"	"Sometimes I work with pretty specialized patient populations, and when the study has a low n it would make me really nervous to share like lesion data and like it would. It would be that almost to the point where you could potentially figure out who they are, if you know where the study was conducted, and kind of some of the specifics of their disease, so I that would make that makes me nervous, especially with the low n."
13	20	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 22:47	B-ID	"I'm worried that you know the more my participants share, the harder it's going to be to completely de-identify them"
13	22	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 22:45	"B-OD, B-SD"	"I do a lot of mixed methods work, and especially in the qualitative portion. I'm worried about that as well. I'm worried that you know the more my participants share, the harder it's going to be to completely de-identify them, and I don't want my participants to have to worry about you know, the what they share in the interview. I don't want them to have to be concerned about like over-sharing or giving me too much information."
13	29	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:18	"F-OD, F-IS"	"This is. I wonder if this is another place where library assistance could help? Like if university libraries had open data, repositories and we didn't have to like, find one. I don't. I don't know if that would be useful."
13	32	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:26	"F-OD, F-NIH, KOP-NIH"	"Well, I think the NIH is changing to require data sharing, so I think that'll be a good facilitator. Anyone who has funding will be forced to."
13	38	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:30	"B-OD, B-ID"	"I was trying to decide how to frame it as a facilitator but I just I don't know if there is a way to like. So our IRB here thinks that audio recordings, and I don't know how true this is for other places, but those are identifiable, especially with the low n like X was saying"
13	40	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:31	"F-OD, F-DID"	So like if there was a way to further de-identify the voices that were...so that it would be less identifiable. Maybe that would be something that would facilitate open data sharing.
13	44	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:00	B-T	"I feel like time is such a barrier, you know. Just one more thing to do"
13	46	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 22:59	B-ID	"And making sure it's de-identified, and you know, like the stress was making sure everything's de-identified"
14	3	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 22:53	B-OD	"I feel like time is such a barrier, you know. Just one more thing to do, like if there's if if it was someone's job to do it, that would be...And making sure it's de-identified, and you know, like the stress was making sure everything's de-identified, taking the time to do that on top of everything else we have to do is faculty, I think. I mean, I think time is a big barrier too with anything that's not required it. It gets pushed and pushed and pushed with everything else that you have to do kind of prioritized."
14	3	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 22:59	B-T	"taking the time to do that on top of everything else we have to do is faculty, I think. I mean, I think time is a big barrier too with anything that's not required it. It gets pushed and pushed and pushed with everything else that you have to do kind of prioritized."
14	7	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:12	KOP-NIH	"there is an autism repository that I I think you're required to. Yeah. The NIH requires that you any data you collect you have to like, put it in this repository"
14	10	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:13	"B-FR, PE-OD"	"And as part of my postdoc, like I had, I was the one who had to format the data for that thing. And it was it was horrible like, and I know we kept. They kept coming back. It was not formatted correctly like, and I had the time like that was like part of my job then"
14	12	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:13	"B-OD, B-T"	"And as part of my postdoc, like I had, I was the one who had to format the data for that thing. And it was it was horrible like, and I know we kept. They kept coming back. It was not formatted correctly like, and I had the time like that was like part of my job then. But I would. That is a barrier to me right now. I like would never want to do that again, because you know it, it was just who's going to do that? It took so much time. So yeah, time is a huge one"
14	15	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:13	U-SA	"I think, like a theme that's coming out of this just like the archiving thing is people are feeling like they don't know what's allowed, and I think, like straightforward like, what are the things that we're allowed to to to archive or not"
14	16	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:14	U-OD	you know what counts as the de-identifiable or not
14	17	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:14	U-OS	"And if that's straightforward across institutions? Which it sounds like, it's not"
14	24	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:34	IOS-RPG	Reduce the research-to-practice gap! Get it out there faster.
14	30	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:34	IOS-T	"I use some some researchers who have put their their research data on online as a teaching tool like for case studies. So you know, it gives me access to better better teaching cases."
14	31	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:35	IOS-RPG	And I think that also helps again reduce that research-to-practice gap because the students are are practicing with real real cases.
14	36	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:37	"IOS-LS, IOS-MA"	"On the research side, it would make, you know, meta analyses easier to do, which maybe help us kind of answer some of those questions that are harder to answer with, like the smaller n. And once you've combined a lot of studies together maybe we can start getting your clearer answers to some of the questions that would help clinicians."
14	39	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:18	IOS-RR	"Replication from different labs to see if the things are actually working, or if it's a researcher influence."
14	42	Micah Hirsch	8/8/2023 22:05	CI-MR	Open data would facilitate secondary data analyses which would make life a lot easier for those of us that aren’t in R1or R2 institutions if we didn't have to collect our own data.
15	3	Brittany Ciullo	7/26/2023 23:28	"CI-MR, CI-PT"	"being able to do research that is, secondary data analysis would be really helpful for me to grow as professional and to, you know, make tenure, and all of those types of things."
15	10	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:06	IOS-LS	"I think this point about especially for clinical research about you know it. People looking at like a small n like X was saying, you know, and and being able to see that across studies, and seeing, oh, this is a consistent finding, especially like clinical finding."
15	17	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:09	IOS-LF	" But some sometimes I feel like communication sciences and disorders were sort of like, I don't know it would legitimize us, I guess. A little bit too like in the field of science, like you know what I mean I sometimes it feels like we're a little slower to jump on these on this stuff like here's where science is headed, and here's where we are, and you know, so I think if we were part of that like it would make people recognize this field as a scientific field of study"
15	28	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:40	CI-PT	I liked what X said earlier about it would make it easier for some of us to get tenure.
15	36	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:42	"CI-PT, CI-MP"	"Especially like X was saying too if I didn't have to conduct a research study every time I needed to publish something. I'm interested in intervention research which takes, you know, a long time to get going, and then maybe I'll get a couple of pubs, but like in the meantime, I have 5 years of work that I have to have publications, and that process can be pretty slow. So if there was a way to access other data or make these connections with secondary analyses, maybe that would be something I could be doing while I was recruiting and and treating participants. So...maybe not early tenure, but at least tenure."
15	38	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:43	CI-MP	"I mean, I think I’d publish more with open data"
15	39	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:43	CI-MC	"I think I'd probably get more citations with open access to my articles, at least, from what I've heard"
15	41	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:49	CI-MT	"If we went back to open educational research resources, I’d probably have more time to conduct research if there were open education resources available."
15	46	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:15	CI-LA	" I just wanna the the the audience thing is huge. I mean, you're gonna like, you know, publishing open access just by definition means that you have a bigger audience and sharing your data with like lots of researchers is really exciting, because I was thinking about like an audience in terms of readership, but also in terms of collaborations"
16	2	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:15	CI-FC	"also in terms of collaborations. You know, like you'd be a way to find out what other people are doing, and vice versa for them to find out what I'm doing, and so that would be really exciting"
16	7	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:27	CI-SR	"If your work is more readily accessible to the people who are directly affected by it, then that influences their perception of you, which influences their willingness to support your future research"
16	7	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:26	IOS-IC	" I think there's potential impacts with like participants and the communities that we're working with like. If your work is more readily accessible to the people who are directly affected by it, then that influences their perception of you, which influences their willingness to support your future research."
16	18	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:50	WTL-OPR	"Open peer review was in that section of like what are things that we want to learn about? I have never heard of that in my life. So I would, I know that we sort of said all of them, but I and it didn't come up in our sort of questions today, but that would be something I'd be interested in like learning more about. And are there journals in our field that do this? I don't know."
16	24	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:53	"B-OPR, B-PD, PE-OPR"	"I was asked to be a reviewer on an open review, and it was for a researcher who I deeply respected, but who scared me, and I decided I did not want to do it, because I didn't want her to, you know, even though I’m sure the review would have been pretty positive. I just didn't want her to associate me with criticizing her work. Granted, she was very senior, and I was a postdoc at the time."
16	36	Danika Pfeiffer	8/10/2023 14:39	F-CR	"I think we need like a repository of lectures and lecture activities and case studies for for, like our field’s teaching, sharing the teaching prep load would be very helpful"
16	37	"Pfeiffer, Danika Lucia - dipalmdl"	7/20/2023 16:58	"CI-MT, IOS-T"	"I think we need like a repository of lectures and lecture activities and case studies for for, like our field’s teaching, sharing the teaching prep load would be very helpful, and giving me more time for for research, and make my teaching more effective."
16	41	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:33	IOS-T	"Sharing assignments on canvas too would be really nice to be able to just have...I don't know, like this one canvas for CSD, where you can pull assignments into your course that are already, you know"
17	2	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:42	"F-OER, F-CR"	"I really wish and hope somebody will go off and get the resources to like build a website where maybe we can sort all of of our instructional, like assignments and syllabi and slides, and all of those things to make the the teaching part more open"
17	3	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:56	IOS-Tr	"I was listening to the discussion of, like the the open reviews, I love the idea of transparency"
17	5	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:53	IOS-RA	"I was listening to the discussion of, like the the open reviews, I love the idea of transparency, especially like for for making people accountable for some of the the harmful and abusive and uninformed things that they say."
17	6	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 15:48	"B-PD, B-OPR"	"But also there's just this huge power differential there. And I wouldn't be able to review for some of the people that I review for, if they knew it was me reviewing for them"
17	14	Micah Hirsch	7/28/2023 16:02	IOS-T	"Yeah, seeing some like more focus on this, I feel like, and I don't know if it's just because I'm new. But I feel like we are...I've noticed that, like people in this kind of generation are more likely to also share the teaching things like I've had several people just offer me materials, and I'm like, oh, my gosh, I can't. This is so wonderful, you know"
