Page	Line	Author	Date & Time	Comment	Reference Text
1	12	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:18	LPE-OS	So I don't know necessarily that I've had any experience with using open science practices.
1	14	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:19	"TE-OA, TE-W"	"I have attended continuing education sessions on how to access research more easily, and to avoid paying for articles and getting around paywalls."
1	15	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:19	LPE-OS	"But other than that, I haven't really had much opportunity."
1	19	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:22	"TE-NE, TE-OS"	"I would second that I would say. During my training, and even through, I would say, local continuing education at my university. I have not had much experience with open science practices."
1	20	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:25	"PE-OA, PE-OM, IOS-Tr"	"I am trying to be more transparent about my work, and like using like posting protocols and trying to publish open access when possible."
1	21	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:26	"B-OD, B-CX"	"And then sharing data is a little more complicated, I would say, from my perspective."
1	31	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:30	"F-OA, F-M"	"And so there's money that researchers can apply for to support open acc...to cover the open access fees for publishing in an open access journal. They also have some. The University has some relationships, I guess, with Elsevier, or other things where we can also publish in certain journals. We can publish in a non- open access journal, but cover the open access fees through that. "
1	31	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:29	"F-IS, F-OA"	"So I work at a university, and our library, our librarians are very active in increasing...sorry my cat...open access, so they do a lot of training. We have an open access publication fund that was supported by the librarians. And so there's money that researchers can apply for to support open acc...to cover the open access fees for publishing in an open access journal. They also have some. The University has some relationships, I guess, with Elsevier, or other things where we can also publish in certain journals. We can publish in a non- open access journal, but cover the open access fees through that. "
1	38	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:30	"F-OA, F-IS"	"And we also have a Scholar Works which is the institutional repository. So when...and I don't know that that's really caught on super widely in the university. But they are trying to do a lot to get the word out that when when researchers, you know whether they be faculty, staff, lecturors at the university publish, they can put them in that repository, and then they're available to people within institution, which, as in, as I understand, is a little more. You know, you can do that before you before the embargo date, since it's not technically public."
1	43	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:31	LPE-OS	"Yeah, i'll go ahead if that's okay. Let's see. I haven't done a whole lot related to open science exactly."
1	44	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:32	"TE-OS, TE-P"	"I've listened to several different podcasts talking about the various aspects of open science, so I feel like I have a decent understanding of the different components of it."
1	45	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:32	LPE-OS	But haven't implemented.
1	46	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:33	"LPE-OD, LPE-OA"	"Let's see, like I haven't posted data publicly before, code or published anything, paid extra to publish open access, or done any registered reports or anything."
2	3	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:34	"PE-SA, B-SA, B-I"	"I tried to put up free, legal versions of previous manuscripts on my department website, but was told that I had to adhere to a particular format that didn't allow for publications to be posted on there. So, as it turns out, I wasn't able to."
2	4	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:35	MUR	But I respond quickly to requests on Research Gate. When people do request articles.
2	6	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:36	MUR	"So, I have tried to post anything I can on my research gate."
2	8	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:38	"PW, PE-PR, PE-OM"	"I don't have a personal website yet, but I have posted preregistrations on OSF and I've posted some R scripts and some stimuli."
2	8	Micah Hirsch	10/10/2023 16:40	_Marked as resolved_	"I don't have a personal website yet, but I have posted preregistrations on OSF and I've posted some R scripts and some stimuli."
2	8	Micah Hirsch	10/10/2023 16:41	_Re-opened_	"I don't have a personal website yet, but I have posted preregistrations on OSF and I've posted some R scripts and some stimuli."
2	8	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:38	LPE-OD	I haven't shared data yet.
2	9	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:39	PE-OA	But have been paying for open access and things like that as well.
2	12	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:41	"PE-OA, PE-SA"	"So yeah, I have published in open science journals and uploaded my papers on Bio archive for public accessibility."
2	13	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:43	IOS-A	I have only heard positive responses from people who have downloaded them and had access to the manuscripts.
2	14	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:43	PE-OM	I've also uploaded stimuli and experiment protocols on Github.
2	15	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:44	"IOS-A, IOS-RR"	"And I do agree with the statement I see here is that it increases the accessibility, transfer, and replicability of science."
2	25	Danika Pfeiffer	9/22/2023 21:09	"TE-W, TE-OS, R-UCSD"	"So I did do a CSDisseminate webinar, maybe"
2	29	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:46	"TE-OS, TE-SA, TE-CS"	"But most of my open science practice knowledge was built individually through conversations with other scientists who were working their way through the process. Or recommended like a research gate for sending articles, or walked me through which exact manuscript draft it was the one to save that could be legally shared. Yeah. and you say it. It's a lot of individual instruction at the beginning."
2	37	Danika Pfeiffer	9/22/2023 21:08	"TE-NE, TE-W, TE-OS, R-UCSD"	"I think I did a CSDisseminate something a webinar, whatever it was some time ago, but otherwise I I mean, I've had very little formal instruction on open science. It wasn't really a model that was emphasized in my Phd training. I didn't really see that from my Phd mentors. "
2	37	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:49	PE-OM	A little bit of OSF. Posting some stimuli there.
2	40	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:50	"TE-NE, TE-OS, TE-P, TE-SM, TE-W, A-OS"	"But it wasn't really emphasized or not right, encouraged very much. So otherwise. Yeah. What, a Webinar here, there, some podcasts, and then seeing things on Twitter. People encouraging open science practices."
2	46	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:51	"TE-OS, TE-NT"	"I'll also add, so I didn't do a postdoc. I went straight from a Ph.D. right into an assistant professor position, and I feel like the friends that I have that are currently in postdocs or just wrapping up have been able to get that training, so I feel like it's blossoming right now and some of us that have graduated, you know, 4 5 6 years ago. Kind of missed the train a little bit on all that training that's coming out."
3	4	Austin Thompson	8/17/2023 17:52	"TE-PR, TE-CS"	"So, someone that I've recently collaborated with that is a postdoc has actually taught me quite a bit, and that's how I've gotten kind of more exposure and comfort with OSF and pre registrations and posting things like that. So? I would agree with X if I'm pronouncing your name correctly? In that it's been a lot of like one-on-one individualized kind of support from colleagues."
3	6	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:08	"TE-OS, TE-CP"	"Yeah, I added, I attended a training session at a conference. It was a formal training session."
3	8	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:09	"TE-OA, TE-CP"	I I attended that conference there was a discussion and the need for open access and all that.
3	9	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:09	"TE-OS, TE-PD"	"So, I I receive formal training during a postdoctal experience."
3	22	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:10	"TE-NT, TE-OS"	"And we, in my PhD program, we haven't talked about open science practices, and it was more my experience with it, is more from when I was wrapping up my clinical practice kind of phase of my career, and where I was sort of reading about, and hearing that this was a way that as a consumer I could sort of get that information. And I have not had much about being like much training about being a producer of science, and how to get that out. There was more about like this is how you can access it when you need it. Not how you get it out."
3	27	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:13	"F-IS, F-OER, TE-OER"	"So my university library has talked about open education resources,"
3	29	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:14	"B-OS, B-OA, B-NE"	"but because my university is not a research focused university, I don't think open access for research is as much of a concern. Especially because our tenure and promotion expectations are going to be lower because we're not a research focused institution."
3	38	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:15	WTL-PR	"I really feel that I would like to know the process. You know, so not just here's the practice. But what is the process around preregistering and submitting."
3	39	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:15	LP-P	"And what exactly, step by step, more procedural, I guess. I'm very good about following procedures."
3	44	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:16	"TE-NT, TE-OS"	"You know I have an ORCID ID, and and that was kind of the focus on my PhD program was making sure we had that. But there was no discussion, as somebody else had mentioned, on open science. It was really...I was at an R1 institution, and it was all about grant writing and and submitting for NIH and all that. I was in implementation science courses. And so that was a whole different beast. "
3	44	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:17	LP-P	"So yeah, I just think a procedure would be very helpful."
4	1	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:17	LP-P	"I would say, in addition to the procedure. I also like like, step by step"
4	4	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:18	"B-OS, B-F, B-KJP"	"and you know, as a pre- tenure assistant professor, I'm also very conscious of making sure that that I have data to publish, and making sure that I'm not just looking negative in any way to potential publishers. And unfortunately, that's just the reality of it."
4	6	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:19	WTL-OS	"However, I would say, all of the above in terms of your list here. I would attend a session on any of this. And also yeah, just knowing my limits and what I can do."
4	6	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:20	LP-P	What's the appropriate step-by-step procedure to follow?
4	10	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:23	"B-SA, B-F"	"Because that's kind of been my limiting factor, and just again making sure I I do it right, and I kind of protect myself pre tenure."
4	10	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:22	"B-KJP, B-SA, LP-PPOV"	"And I would love to hear that from a publisher standpoint. I would love to hear from. You know someone who who does work for a peer-reviewed publication to say, this is okay, this is not. Because that's kind of been my limiting factor, and just again making sure I I do it right, and I kind of protect myself pre tenure."
4	17	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:23	"B-SA, B-F, B-KJP"	"I agree with that. I would also say that the self-archiving piece always kind of makes me worry that someone mentioned previously about which version you're going to put out there, and I'm always really nervous unless I have an open access paper that I paid for. I know I can put that anywhere, but if it's not open access like which version can I put up individual independently, because I don't want to like have to go to court because I did something wrong. I'm probably catastrophizing it, but that for me."
4	19	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:24	LP-P	"Procedurally I've learned about it, but it would be really great to have like a step-by-step like this is the version you upload. If you have this kind of level of copyright, etc.,"
4	23	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:24	LP-PPOV	I'd like to to add that not only would it be helpful to hear it from the publisher's point of view. 
4	24	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:26	WTL-IP	"But I would really, really love a talk through on each of those topics. That's specific to my institution. "
4	27	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:26	"B-R, B-OS, B-OD"	Because I really do feel often that I am fighting a fight without the support of the librarians that that would be so beneficial to me. Which person do I need to talk to? To talk about the open data processes within my institution. Which person do I need to talk to? For. Yeah. You get the idea.
4	31	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:27	"WTL-OA, WTL-IP, B-OA, B-M"	"For me, You know. I'm curious about like how to kind of manage the cost of publishing open access. Because typically, just to publish doesn't cost anything but making it open access adds a cost. So, I don't know if my university would be willing to cover that."
4	34	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:28	"B-OD, B-IRB, B-F"	"Additionally, you know, my IRB, sometimes I I perceive them as kind of like worrying about things excessively. So if I were to share data openly, I'm worried that the IRB would shut that down at my university, or I would face backlash from them."
4	36	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:28	LP-P	"Yeah, so I think like just kind of knowing how to navigate those issues would be helpful for me to know, kind of like the best place to start, and then the best way to move forward with it."
4	46	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:30	"WTL-OD, WTL-IRB, P-OD"	"So similarly. Yeah, from the IRB perspective, just knowing if it's okay to post the identified data publicly. If I didn't explicitly, write that in the IRB. And in the consent form. Yeah, is a question of mine,"
5	3	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:31	"WTL-SA, PE-SA, U-SA"	" and then in terms of self archiving. So I've done preprints before, but I'm always sort of unclear about okay. Once that actually gets accepted and published. What do I do with the preprint? Do I leave it up? Do I update it? Do I take it down? I don't know. I could probably figure it out. But I don't know at this point."
5	4	Austin Thompson	8/18/2023 14:31	WTL-OER	"And then, in terms of another topic, open educational resources is something I don't know a whole lot about from this list."
5	14	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:38	"LP-W, LP-I"	"Yeah, for me. Just the way, I learn an interactive workshop would be best for me, which I know takes more time. But you know, having something where I get to walk through what that process looks like with someone have a live discussion about it. Which you don't, get that like always good question and answer within a live webinar and you don't have that opportunity within a pre-recorded webinar."
5	14	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:38	LP-H	Handouts.
5	28	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:41	LP-V	"I would just add Youtube videos, I mean, I know that those are, you know. It's nice to have something where you can jump around pretty easily. So Youtube videos that are tagged with chapters or things like that so you can listen to a little bit at a time. Or find the bit that you need. I think, sometimes pre recorded webinars, it's a little bit more difficult, depending on the format, for me to find the information that I need within the the Webinar. So Youtube videos tend to break things down, and sometimes I don't have more than 5 minutes, you know, between jumping around with different tasks"
5	28	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:41	LP-S	"So Youtube videos tend to break things down, and sometimes I don't have more than 5 minutes, you know, between jumping around with different tasks, to be able to find what I need."
5	32	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:42	"LP-I, LP-W, LP-H, LP-V"	"Yeah. So sorry I'll add my 2 cents that interactive workshop, handouts, and Youtube videos are three avenues that I use regularly to learn from. So, if it was in at least those three formats, it would be helpful to me."
5	37	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:48	"LP-V, LP-H"	"I agree. I like that, you know, with with handouts and Youtube videos specifically. You know, you can access those when you're ready for the information, because I think you know, open science as a whole is a very big, broad topic. And so, you know. Being able to target those, like someone you had mentioned like tagged sections."
5	39	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:48	LP-A	"I think it's really helpful to get that information when you need it, and I think that's been a contributing factor to me not attending webinars in the past, just because I wasn't ready for the information."
5	41	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:49	LP-A	I think also just ease of finding prerecorded webinars is sometimes difficult.
5	43	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:49	LP-S	Or just having them in really short snippet. So here's a 5 minute introduction on X or on Y
6	1	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:50	LP-H	"and then, having, you know, a handout that's related to it, so that you have, like the step-by-step on a piece of paper that you could potentially follow along with while you're watching the Youtube video or just as a reminder, of after I've watched the YouTube video, this is my step-by-step, for you know, uploading a preregistration or something like that"
6	1	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:49	LP-V	"And I agree that being able to kind of jump around in a Youtube video is really nice. Or just having them in really short snippet. So here's a 5 minute introduction on X or on Y, and then, having, you know, a handout that's related to it, so that you have, like the step-by-step on a piece of paper that you could potentially follow along with while you're watching the Youtube video or just as a reminder, of after I've watched the YouTube video, this is my step-by-step, for you know, uploading a preregistration or something like that."
6	11	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:52	"LP-WG, LP-I"	"as I'm going through this for my purposes and learning to to go through the open science from the beginning of an experiment, research project, whatever, to the end it would be like, it would be beneficial to have like a cohort group of hey, i'm going to start an open science project, and we'll meet once a month between this time and this time. And where are you? What do you need? What's the current problem? Just to to, like an interactive work group, rather than a workshop."
6	24	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:55	B-PR	So I I'll I'll. My contribution is really short. It's just honestly my own organizational practices are the biggest barrier for me preregistering.
6	24	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:55	B-LOO	It's just honestly my own organizational practices are the biggest barrier for me preregistering.
6	27	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 18:56	"B-PR, B-F"	It's kind of the vulnerability of posting your ideas before you've done this study.
6	31	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:02	"PE-PR, B-PD"	"And, you know I have been in a situation where we preregistered the protocol, and also published the protocol for something, and I mean a peer viewer should have recused themself but they tried to to deny the article or reject the article because they were doing something similar. So it was kind of a weird situation, and so that kind of left a bad taste in my mouth."
6	33	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:04	KOP-PR	I think there's also different stages where you can preregister.
6	38	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:05	"F-DC, F-PR"	"So I find it a good time to preregister is when you’ve collected the data, but you haven't analyzed it yet. So you like, kind of have a sense of like what your age group is, and how many kids, I work with kids. How many kids you've already recruited to participate. So, like you haven't done any of like the data cleaning or the data processing or the analyses. So you still have really sound research questions, hypotheses, and methods. But you've already kind of collected the data."
6	39	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:06	PE-PR	"So I find it a good time to preregister is when you’ve collected the data, but you haven't analyzed it yet. So you like, kind of have a sense of like what your age group is, and how many kids, I work with kids. How many kids you've already recruited to participate. So, like you haven't done any of like the data cleaning or the data processing or the analyses. So you still have really sound research questions, hypotheses, and methods. But you've already kind of collected the data. So, the most recent preregistration I did, we did it in that format."
6	41	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:08	LP-C	And so also create the education around. What types of pre registrations out there. When is it a good time to pre register to kind of help with some of those barriers.
6	42	Danika Pfeiffer	10/3/2023 23:20	"CI-A, F-PR"	"But I think for me, I actually find it a huge advantage because it really gets you set up to get ready to go."
6	44	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:09	"B-LOO, B-T, B-PR"	But I agree with the previous comment that just getting yourself organized and put together like even writing the preregistration can take weeks to get yourself set up and ready to go
7	2	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:13	"B-PR, B-CM"	"If there's any changes from your preregistration, and you're writing it in your manuscript, you tend to have to take the space to then explain that the differences between what you preregistered and what actually happened. So, depending on word count and things like that that could potentially be a barrier."
7	9	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:18	"F-B, F-PR"	"So I think I would be motivated by, if there is some sort of direct benefit to me of doing this,"
7	11	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:18	"B-PR, B-NE"	"because right now I feel like I'm I lack the motivation to do right preregistration, because it's not something that is, looked for, say, in my promotion or tenure reviews, and it's not valued by my university."
7	12	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:20	"F-PR, F-E"	"So, if it were something that became an expectation within my department or college or university."
7	19	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:23	U-PR	"I do have a question about this process like when I write IRBs, I'm doing all of this. Like, I've taken the time to write the research question and the methods. And you know, then, once it gets approved and all those forms are in place, then I would feel comfortable. I don't know copying, or having IRB send that information to preregister."
7	20	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:24	"B-PR, B-T"	"But having to duplicate that work. You know, I don't have time for that, as some of you've already said,"
7	22	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:24	U-PR	so does anyone know if there's sort of like this once you've been approved by IRB whether that information can be sent as a preregistration for this process?
7	30	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:26	A-OD	The only thing different is that I'd say my main source of familiarity with open access is  through the talk bank records.
7	38	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:28	B-KJP	"It kind of came up earlier, but just keeping track of what versions are allowed for which journal. "
7	40	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:26	B-SA	"It kind of came up earlier, but just keeping track of what versions are allowed for which journal. And every time I look into, you know, dig into the requirements for the journal, and I pull up the page, and I use the site that you can search for requirements. And still, it's really confusing to me."
7	40	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:27	B-CX	"And every time I look into, you know, dig into the requirements for the journal, and I pull up the page, and I use the site that you can search for requirements. And still, it's really confusing to me."
7	42	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:29	"PE-SA, PE-NIH"	"And then, so most of my work has been NIH-funded, which typically allows for open access after a year. So, I've sort of defaulted to, well, I'll just wait a year, and then I can make that version available."
8	1	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:36	"B-T, PW"	"I think this also came up earlier, but just having the time also to make a personal website."
8	4	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:41	B-I	The university has a special format of how they want you to have your profile set up on the University website. So there's limitations to perhaps what can be posted there.
8	6	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:43	"PE-SA, PW, B-T"	"So yeah, I I did make myself a personal website, and it does take a lot of time and work, and<P>kind of wonder if it's really, you know, worth it."
8	6	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:41	B-SA	"I think this also came up earlier, but just having the time also to make a personal website. Some like, I think it was X who mentioned that that there's some, you know, formats. The university has a special format of how they want you to have your profile set up on the University website. So there's limitations to perhaps what can be posted there.<P>So yeah, I I did make myself a personal website, and it does take a lot of time and work, and<P>kind of wonder if it's really, you know, worth it. But that's that's my main area."
8	15	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:44	"F-SA, F-IS, PE-SA"	"My previous institution had a very active librarian and a seamless, like, once a quarter we got a reminder email. Hey? Have you gotten any articles submitted or published? Would you like to archive them? And all I had to do was send them the title and the the journal, and they did all the contacting and figured out which draft needed to be...it was wonderful."
8	24	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:47	U-SA	"I'm like I don't actually know how to get this done the standard way, let alone this more equitable, open access way which I believe in. I just am still feel like I'm figuring out sort of the rules of the road, like the road more traveled."
8	30	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:49	B-CX	"And so I just need to understand, like for me, facilitating this process would be. I need to figure out what is my hierarchy? Who do I talk to? How do I get this all figured out?  Which could be a me problem and it's not something that everyone else deals with. But...it's...there's just a lot out there. Of like layers."
8	30	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:48	"B-SA, B-I"	"The other element of this is that I am at a university that is a regional campus of a flagship state school. And so there's department, college, university here and then there is what we jokingly refer to as the mothership downstate. And then there's all of their rules. And so I just need to understand, like for me, facilitating this process would be. I need to figure out what is my hierarchy? Who do I talk to? How do I get this all figured out?  Which could be a me problem and it's not something that everyone else deals with. But...it's...there's just a lot out there. Of like layers."
8	34	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:50	M-SA	"In I think my first year of my faculty position I was really motivated to self-archive, and have, you know, really accessible on my website a list of all of my manuscripts that are available."
8	42	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:49	B-SA	"Yeah, to kinda to follow up to that comment. In I think my first year of my faculty position I was really motivated to self-archive, and have, you know, really accessible on my website a list of all of my manuscripts that are available. And so, I had a grad student take some time, and you know, figure out the requirements to the best of her knowledge, and tell me which copies of things. And so then I went to the person who manages the faculty websites, and said, hey, I want to do this thing. It's this movement within the field to be more transparent, open. And she said. Oh, well, a lot of faculty end up forgetting to update their manuscript list, so we just don't allow them to be posted at all. So like well, you know. So that was just one example of trying to put in the work and then meeting resistance due to all of these layers, and figuring. Well, you know. This should be a straightforward thing. But there's all these things that make it difficult to actually implement."
8	42	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:51	B-I	"And so then I went to the person who manages the faculty websites, and said, hey, I want to do this thing. It's this movement within the field to be more transparent, open. And she said. Oh, well, a lot of faculty end up forgetting to update their manuscript list, so we just don't allow them to be posted at all. So like well, you know. So that was just one example of trying to put in the work and then meeting resistance due to all of these layers, and figuring. Well, you know. This should be a straightforward thing. But there's all these things that make it difficult to actually implement."
8	42	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:51	PE-SA	"In I think my first year of my faculty position I was really motivated to self-archive, and have, you know, really accessible on my website a list of all of my manuscripts that are available. And so, I had a grad student take some time, and you know, figure out the requirements to the best of her knowledge, and tell me which copies of things. And so then I went to the person who manages the faculty websites, and said, hey, I want to do this thing. It's this movement within the field to be more transparent, open. And she said. Oh, well, a lot of faculty end up forgetting to update their manuscript list, so we just don't allow them to be posted at all. So like well, you know. So that was just one example of trying to put in the work and then meeting resistance due to all of these layers, and figuring. Well, you know. This should be a straightforward thing. But there's all these things that make it difficult to actually implement."
8	42	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:52	B-CX	This should be a straightforward thing. But there's all these things that make it difficult to actually implement.
9	5	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:52	PE-OA	"But in my department we're really lucky that we have a clinic that makes a little bit of money, and we're actually able to pay."
9	7	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:52	"B-OA, B-M"	"I think the biggest barrier is, where do you find the funds to be able to pay for open access? I think that's the biggest in smaller departments like ours."
9	11	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:57	"B-OA, B-M, B-R"	"I would add that that the funding is a huge issue. Specifically, when you're not in an R rated institution right? Because we don't have research assistance. We don't have lab space. We don't have let alone, just flat out cash to pay for an open access readership."
9	17	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:57	"B-OA, B-M"	"That's what I was gonna share is just the cost associated with it. My university university doesn't have a lot of funding. I have no experience with grant writing, so I don't even really know how to access funding for opportunities like this."
9	17	Austin Thompson	8/14/2023 19:58	U-OA	"I have no experience with grant writing, so I don't even really know how to access funding for opportunities like this."
9	32	Micah Hirsch	8/16/2023 23:26	"F-OA, F-M"	"I would say. A facilitator has been when I have grant funds, and I can pay for it."
9	34	Austin Thompson	8/24/2023 16:45	"B-OA, B-R, B-M"	"But you know I I am at an institution that it's an R2, specifically, and the vibe here has always been uou pay for it yourself."
9	40	Micah Hirsch	8/16/2023 23:35	"F-OA,F-IS, F-M"	"Also, if you know, the Dean of the college is willing to put his or her money where his or her mouth is, or their money, in terms of having a pot of money for faculty to pull from. I think X had previously mentioned that at her institution their library has some money to pay for open access."
9	43	Austin Thompson	8/24/2023 16:43	"B-OA, B-M, B-R"	"I know my library also has that, but the money is distributed equally between authors. So if there's three authors on my paper, my library is only going to pay for the one-third for me, and then the other 2 thirds, even even if I'm first author, then the other 2 thirds need to be covered by someone else. So that makes it a little bit difficult at my institution."
9	45	Micah Hirsch	8/16/2023 23:36	"F-OA, F-M, F-IS"	"So having a pot of money either at the library or within the Dean's office, would be really helpful.<P>"
10	9	Micah Hirsch	8/16/2023 23:38	"B-OA, B-M, IE-OA"	" maybe this is just me being idealistic, but you know we already don't get any financial kickback from publishing, and so I feel like the cost associated with publishing open access is pretty inequitable. We, I mean, at my university unfortunately, like we are, we we don't get paid like a very high salary and trying to bridge that research to practice gap through open access, then basically punishing us by making us pay for something when we already don't get any monetary gain from publishing it. Personally, it makes no sense to me, so I don't see like, if the idea is open access, then why do we have to pay still for open access? That seems like it doesn't accomplish the spirit of open access science."
10	16	Micah Hirsch	8/16/2023 23:45	IE-OA	"So just add to that, I would also say, I also think it kind of defeats the purpose of open access, and that it's supposed to be for everyone and make this, I would think, a more like transparent and diversified research environment where it, when it's paid for it, kind of limits who can participate in that. And what type of research is even getting published on it."
10	26	Danika Pfeiffer	9/22/2023 21:11	"B-LOB, B-NE"	"I don't perceive a lot of benefit to myself, and that sounds selfish because it is, but I have to watch out for my own time. And so yeah, I just don't see a lot of external motivation,"
10	28	Micah Hirsch	8/16/2023 23:51	B-OD	"I don't perceive a lot of benefit to myself, and that sounds selfish because it is, but I have to watch out for my own time. And so yeah, I just don't see a lot of external motivation, and it’s opening up myself up to potential criticism. Not that I think that there's anything wrong with my stimuli. But yeah, just lack of external motivation or incentives."
10	28	Danika Pfeiffer	9/22/2023 21:10	"B-LOB, B-NE"	"But yeah, just lack of external motivation or incentives."
10	32	Micah Hirsch	8/16/2023 23:52	"B-OD, B-T"	"I think also in terms of protocols or more of like my R syntax, or something like that, is taking the time to clean it up. Rather than like the shorthand that it's currently in to be able to make it readable by someone else, just taking the time to to clean it up and make it public facing"
10	39	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:01	"F-OD, F-W, F-KOP"	"I know a lot of grant applications these days do require you to have some kind of data management policy, particularly with the focus on open data and data sharing. So I think just a better maybe understanding of what the...you know, what's required in terms of the the funders and grantors. And what what kind of data they want us to share, and where they'd like us to share it."
10	43	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:01	"B-OD, B-R"	"As as supportive as our library is our ITS is maybe not so much so. We don't have access to some of the the programs like. Of course, now I can't think of it. We have Qualtrics, but we don't have what's it called? Red Cap. Thank you. Because they have some concerns about you know, anyways. So that's been the the bane of my existence recently, but just having access to some of those database programs as well."
11	5	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:07	F-KOP	More knowledge
11	5	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:07	F-OD	More knowledge. an existing infrastructure
11	5	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:07	F-CR	an existing infrastructure
11	10	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:13	F-KOP	Like what is best practice? I think there is another comment in the chat about that. Like how to best do it.
11	11	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:13	F-NIH	"I know some NIH institutes have repositories and have it very clearly spelled out, while other institutes leave you to your own devices to do it"
11	12	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:13	F-KOP	So how do we go about doing it? Because it is required by many grants now.
11	12	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:13	F-OD	" Like what is best practice? I think there is another comment in the chat about that. Like how to best do it. I know some NIH institutes have repositories and have it very clearly spelled out, while other institutes leave you to your own devices to do it. So how do we go about doing it? Because it is required by many grants now."
11	20	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:15	"F-OD, F-NIH"	"I think the you know direction NIH is going is really going to be a benefit as as money growing pains as it gave me at the beginning of this year. You know I do think it's going to encourage our institutions to kind of step up to the plate a little bit in, you know, helping to facilitate open data."
11	29	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:16	IOS-RR	"I guess it will facilitate a lot of replication studies. You can use the same stimuli, same protocol. Everything is available online. You can use it. Say, like a different population of same population that replicate those results"
11	32	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:16	IOS-RPG	I would hope it would also facilitate research getting to practice more quickly as clinicians could locate things without cost to themselves.
11	44	Micah Hirsch	8/17/2023 0:20	IOS-Tr	"I think that there's also an element of sharing what the research process is truly like with clinicians. I know as a clinician I didn't completely understand, like, in order to get through IRB or in order to move the publication process along exactly how narrow any given research study needed to be. And I think the more that clinicians, we pull back the veil a little bit on like how the science is produced. Then clinicians can better understand, like how this is being created. And so, then there is mutual understanding on both sides of, we want you to have access to the science. We want you to know how we create the science. Or, you know, discover things. So I just think it makes it just a little bit more. Hmm. Knowledge. There's more knowledge for everyone in in the procedures of it all."
12	2	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:07	IOS-T	"I also use it in my teaching. So, getting, introducing all of the things that were just spoken to students, before they're clinicians."
12	9	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:07	IOS-SIR	"That's what I was going to say was getting students interested in and acclimated to research and showing them that it doesn't have to be this big scary process. I think data collection can feeI, I know for me, when I was a student researcher, that data collection was really overwhelming. As well as developing methodology. So, seeing what's out there, and seeing how I can tweak it to my interests, I think would have... I was really interested but I think it might have recruited more of my classmates into research."
12	18	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:10	IOS-LS	"Also, just to add that you know, in our field we tend to have fairly small N studies just because of accessibility of research participants. And so you know the more that we share things openly, particularly data in that sense, it's easier to combine results from different studies to to sort of answer, maybe different questions than we could answer individually in our little, you know, silos."
12	24	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:10	CI-FC	"I think it might be a good way to meet collaborators and maybe expand what you're looking at, and who you're working with."
12	29	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:12	CI-MR	"I guess it should have helped me in taking up projects that you know I I didn't have enough technical skills on. If I had the protocol ready stimulus ready from somebody else... in general, it would have helped me in taking up more projects that conceptually make sense to me, but not really have matlab skills or python skills to run the protocols."
12	33	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:17	CI-MR	I think it could help cut down on redundancy of lots of research groups doing the same sort of work in terms of getting stimuli processed and recorded and edited and cut out all that sort of extra work and allow us to focus more on doing the actual research
12	37	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:21	CI-SR	"in terms of me, potentially doing more open science practices, I think it could potentially help people to have more faith in the type of research that I'm doing and view me as a stronger researcher if I'm consistently doing more of these open science practices, potentially. If it becomes something that people value more and becomes more common."
12	41	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:27	CI-MC	"I know some institutions really look at the H index and things like that like how often you're being cited, and so, if more work is open access, then more people can cite your work"
12	43	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:28	CI-LA	"And then that kind of boosts those scores for those institutions that are really looking for you to have a really broad reach, rather, whether it's nationally or internationally"
12	43	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:27	CI-PT	"Also for some it might help with the tenure process. I know some institutions really look at the H index and things like that like how often you're being cited, and so, if more work is open access, then more people can cite your work. And then that kind of boosts those scores for those institutions that are really looking for you to have a really broad reach, rather, whether it's nationally or internationally, to show that your your work is having an impact in your field."
12	46	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:33	CI-LA	"I think the research that I have done, and I'm going to be doing is really cool, and I want other people to read it"
13	4	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:33	CI-LA	so getting my name out there and letting people see what I've done. And then just becoming like a name in the field. That's one of my career aspirations.
13	14	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:37	WTL-OS	"I would just be...like, I'm just curious about what open science looks like within other fields. And how our field compares. Because typically, since we're newer, we're a little bit behind. And so I'm curious to see like what other fields of research and what other professions have embraced open science and what that looks like for them."
13	19	Danika Pfeiffer	9/22/2023 21:36	"F-OS, F-CS"	"I just suggested that if there's any way to get a list of mentors, let's say, maybe in a different category of institutions."
13	21	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:41	"B-OS, B-KOP"	"Like I'm at an R2 institution. So we're...and I’d done my PhD in an R1, and I found that just that little change in category makes a huge difference in what's available to us, as far as knowledge and process and procedures"
13	23	Danika Pfeiffer	9/22/2023 21:36	"F-OS, F-CS"	"So having, maybe somebody who is in our particular institutional category to help step us through maybe some unique procedures and processes that are preventing us from being more involved."
13	32	Brittany Ciullo	8/17/2023 22:45	"F-OS, F-CR"	"I'm, thinking in terms of resources for those of us whose institutions are less familiar with open science, it may be helpful just to have a a list or some sort of reference, to be able to give to our institutions, or give to our library, saying why this is important. You know, what are the benefits, and what are the barriers, so that you know, it's not just each of us fighting the fight individually."
